<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE narrative [
    <!ELEMENT stage ANY>
]>
<narrative>
    <stage monster="{060F70EA-8A92-4117-AB65-75DE3458E407}">
    </stage>
    <stage monster="{AFF2D1F2-DDA4-4A57-84F8-A240B4A0476D}">
    </stage>
    <stage monster="{40F4380C-7A27-42D6-8F69-E3D60A83CAB1}">
    </stage>

    <monologue end="false" win="false">
        <entry>“Hi, welcome to The Qave by Qennies.”</entry>
        <entry>I had only been working here for a few weeks but I already had the “suggested” customer greeting burned into my memory.</entry>
        <entry>This was one of my manager’s many rules that I was required to follow if I didn’t want to lose my job.</entry>
        <entry>As annoying as my manager’s rules could be, I actually really liked working the late shift at The Qave.</entry>
        <entry>It was never busy at this hour so I always had a lot of time to relax and work on personal projects.</entry>
        <entry>The only thing that wasn’t too awesome about the late shift was the customers.</entry>
        <entry>The few customers that did come through at this hour almost always had MONSTROUS appetites,</entry>
        <entry>and it’s even worse if you get their order wrong.</entry>
        <entry>On top of that, the only people looking for food at this hour were REALLY weird.</entry>
        <entry>“It’s a good thing you like weird people.” I spoke aloud to myself.</entry>
        <entry>I nervously scanned the room, making sure that no one was there to hear me.</entry>
        <entry>Confident that I was alone, I started thinking about all the weird</entry>
        <entry>but cute people I might meet tonight.</entry>
        <entry>Maybe if I was lucky I would hit it off with a CUUUTE customer!</entry>
        <entry>Work probably isn’t the best place for romance but if I could get their number,</entry>
        <entry>maybe I could schedule a date?</entry>
        <entry>While I was thinking about all of the weird but cute customers I might meet, and how I could seduce them,</entry>
        <entry>I heard the door open and the first customer of my shift entered.</entry>
    </monologue>

    <monologue end="true" win="false">
        <entry>I don’t know how I survived the night, but my shift was finally over.</entry>
        <entry>I was supposed to clean up but there was no way I was doing all that work by myself,</entry>
        <entry>the morning shift could take care of it.</entry>
        <entry>As I started packing up to leave for the night, I noticed my notepad.</entry>
        <entry>It was soaked with water, singed in a few places, and completely covered in bite marks.</entry>
        <entry>With a sigh, I set the notepad down, grabbed my stuff and wandered out into the darkness of the early morning hours.</entry>
    </monologue>

    <monologue end="true" win="true">
        <entry>It had been a LOOOOOOONG night but, my shift was finally over.</entry>
        <entry>As I began to clean up, I thought about the customers that had come in tonight. I hoped that I hadn’t upset any of them.</entry>
        <entry>Mop in hand, I whispered aloud to myself, “You did your best, that’s all they can ask of you.”</entry>
        <entry>When the cleaning was finished I started to pack up my stuff, getting ready to leave for the night.</entry>
        <entry>I was taking off my name tag when I noticed my notepad on the counter.</entry>
        <entry>Looking it over, I saw the numbers of some of the customers that I had served tonight.</entry>
        <entry>I found myself reaching for the phone as I read the numbers aloud.</entry>
        <entry>I was going to ask one of these monsters I had met tonight to go on a date but, first I had to make a choice.</entry>
        <entry>Which one do I call?</entry>
    </monologue>
</narrative>